and...
そして...
This is...
これが...
Ah... it hurts...
あ... 痛い...
it hurts...
痛い...
it hurts
痛い
...
I feel a little sore
気 が少し痛い
...
It hurts
痛 いです
...
a...
あ...
this...
これ...
Afu
あ ふ
Don't do it because it's gone!
れて いるからいけない!
Do you like the top?
上がいい?
So
そ
It's hard to pay attention to things like this.
こ だと注意しづらい
I'll bring it over here and lick it from above.
俺 がこっちに持ってくるから上から舐めるって
I got in with the highest popularity, and one person greeted me with my face,
1人気上位で入れて、1人僕の顔の上で迎え合ってもらって、
Do you want me to chew your breasts or drink your breasts?
チューしたりおっぱい飲んだりっていうのをやってもらう?
Last time I finished first, so I want to finish last.
前 回先フィニッシュだったから最後フィニッシュにしたいから
I had the procedure explained first, and Yoko-chan even climbed on top of me.
最 初に手順を入れてもらって、 ヨコちゃんは俺の上に乗っても
I asked her to ride on the other side.
ら って、あっち側に乗ってもらって、
That's why.
わけです